nfinancecenter.com 2017-04-01

# Privacy – Fast way to Financial Freedom – nfinancecenter.com

**Personal Information**  
At various locations on our websites, such as in registration forms, sweepstakes entries, message boards, online stores, surveys, and polls, we may request that you supply us with “personal information,” such as your name, email address, mailing and shipping addresses, home or work telephone number, and/or credit card information. You will always know when we are collecting personal information, because we only collect personal information when you voluntarily submit it to us through our online forms and questionnaires. Although you do not have to provide us with any information to visit our websites, you may not be able to fully utilize all of the services on our websites if you choose not to provide certain information. If you do choose to give us personal information through our websites, we will collect and retain that information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not use cookies on this site.  
Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.  
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by hohogame.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that nfinancecenter.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the news so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Final Notes**  
nfinancecenter.com will never, under any circumstances give away or displays your IP address. Additionally, nfinancecenter.com will never sell or transmit e-mail addresses or any other personal identifiers to 3rd parties. Use of the registration system is optional; however it does maximize the user’s experience here at the site.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us,please send your email to ad@nfinancecenter.com.Thank you for your cooperation.
